Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers - Photographs
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series I: Governor’s Papers
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Meet the Press with Governor Alexander and Secretary William J. Bennett, Washington, DC, May 18, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Bruce C. Allbright, Target Stores (Headshots), May 22, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Tennessee/Japan Reception and Dinner, May 27, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Volunteer Girls’ State, Keynote Address; Lunch with Japanese Ambassador Nobuo Matsunaga at Residence, May 29, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Statehood Celebration, Blount Mansion; Unveiling of State Homecoming Quilt; Cutting of Tennessee’s 190th Birthday Cake, June 1, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Sunset Symphony, Governor Alexander Playing Piano; Governor Alexander in Library and Music Class, June 2, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Proclamation with Judge Ernest Pelligrin, June 3, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Governor Alexander and Japanese Middle Managers, June 19, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Festival of American Folklife; CNN and Nightwatch, June 25, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Department of Personnel Service Awards, June 30, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Winner of the Great American Quilt Contest; Proclamations; Miss Tennessee National Teenager, July 1, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Visit to UT Martin and Address to the Governor’s School for the Humanities; Visit to Governor’s School for International Studies, July 3, 1986 (Box 24)
    - July 4th Activities; Walking in Parade; White House, Tennessee Picnic and Library, July 4, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Statewide Interdepartmental Conference; Banner Minority Youth Program Participants; Meet with Commissioner Bill Long and Toshiba Representatives; American History Students with Don Jackson, July 9, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Governor’s School for the Sciences, July 10, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Governor’s School for the Arts Performances, July 11, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Volunteer Jam XII, Starwood Amphitheatre; Presentation of Pride of Tennessee Certificate to Charlie Daniels, July 12, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Visit with Cavan Hogue, Australian Ambassador, July 15, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Remarks at the Chief Education Officer Leadership Institute; Governor Presents Award to Tennessee Safety Congress, July 21, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Staff Picnic; Certificate Presentation, July 23, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Tennessee Festival, Ballet, Tennessee “No” Team, July 24, 1986 (Box 25)
    - C-Span with Tennessee Tomorrow Students and Teachers, Governor and Commissioner Robert L. McElrath, July 25, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Governor’s Academy for Teachers of Writing, July 28, 1986 (Box 25)
    - National Press Club Reception and Speech, July 30, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Remarks at the Chief Education Officer Leadership Institute; Proclamations, July 31, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Swearing in of Talmadge Gilley, Commissioner of Financial Institutions; Gilley Headshots; Lou Conner and Japanese Visitor, August 1, 1986 (Box 25)
    - The Business and Government Forum Reception, August 5, 1986 (Box 25)
    - 2nd Annual Tennessee Republican Leadership Conference, August 9, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Arts Reception and Awards Presentation; Charity Fund; Homecoming ’86 Announcement of Half Time at the Liberty Bowl; Frank Bumstead and Michael Noir, Minister of Trade, France, August 18, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Proclamations, August 19, 1986 (Box 25)
    - August 22-26, 1986 (3 Folders) National Governor’s Association Summer Meeting, Hilton Head, South Carolina “Good Morning America” Interview (Box 25)
    - Commissioner Talmadge Gilley and 3rd National Bank Representatives; Bill Plunkett and Children, September 2, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Press Conference and Presentation of Day Care Task Force Report, September 3, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Tennessee Education Association Leaders Meeting; Governor Alexander is Presented with 1986 National Conservation Achievement Award by National Wildlife Federation, September 4, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Katherine and Leslie Headshots, September 9, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Dinner with China/Russia Group, September 12, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Dedication Convocation of Jack C. Massey School of Business, Belmont University, September 17, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Remarks at the J.C. Bradford Institutional Conference, September 18, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Governor’s Address to the Managing Editors of the Associated Press, September 20, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Honey Alexander with Ballet Poster and Just Say No Club Member; State Dinner for Phillip Moffitt and Charles Whittle, September 23, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Brother Industries Representatives; National Newspaper Association 101st Annual Convention; Service Awards; Presentation of Governor’s Trophy for Dairy Products, September 25, 1986 (Box 25)
    - 108th General Conference of the National Guard Association; Management Conference Reception; Beech High School Students, September 29, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Roundtable Reception, September 30, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Mitsui Company Representatives with Governor Alexander, the Mayor Oak Ridge and Clark Huffman of the U.S. Department of Energy, October 2, 1986 (Box 25)
    - National Storytelling Festival, Jonesborough, Tennessee, October 3, 1986 (Box 25)
    - (2 Folders) Tennessee Literary Festival, Book and Author Signing, Dinner and Reception, October 9, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Meeting with Japanese Journalists; Taping of “Firing Line” with Governor Alexander, Howard Baker, and William Buckley, October 10, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Chattanooga Rotary Club; Miss America Homecoming Parade; Tennessee Outstanding Achievement Award Presented to Kellye Cash, October 16, 1986 (Box 25)
    - (2 Folders) Thompson and Green Machine Company Representatives; Lunch with Will’s (Alexander) 1st Grade Class, October 17, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Goals for Memphis Forum; Lambuth College, October 23, 1986 (Box 25)
    - (2 Folders) Meeting with Mr. Nagawa and Bill Long; Halloween Costumes, October 31, 1986 (Box 25)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Governor Alexander meets with Governor-Elect Ned McWherter, November 5, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Proclamations, November 12, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Presentation of the Vanderbilt University School of Law Distinguished Community Service Award to Governor Alexander; Southern Legislators Conference on Children and Youth; Reception at Governor’s Residence, November 17, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Visit to Ripley High School and Ripley Square, November 19, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Walk to Henning City Limits; Meet with Alex Haley; Haley House Museum Dedication, November 20, 1986 (Box 26)
    - (2 Folders) Walk through Siam, Visit to Siam Middle School, Visit to East Side Elementary School; Walk through Watauga, Visit to Range Elementary School, November 23-25, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Presentation of Tennessean Outdoors Report; Presentation of Certificate to Kyung Hwan Chin and Shin Soon Im, Metropolitan Life Representative; Proclamations, November 26, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Governor Alexander and Frank Robinson in Watauga, Tennessee, November 30, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Overton High School Choral Group, December 2, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Metro Schools Chorus at Residence; Decoration Group at Residence, December 4, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Glencliff High School Choral Group, December 9, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Cora Howe School Choral Group, December 11, 1986 (Box 26)
    - (3 Folders) Walk through Ooltewah, Visit to Courthouse, Visit to Middle School and Elementary School and High School, Visit to Chapel; Walk through Murfreesboro, Visit to Central Middle School and Oakland High School and Lascassas Elementary School, December 15-17, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Franklin Middle School Choral Group, December 16, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Westwood Jr. High School Choral Group, December 18, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Proclamation for Cattleman’s Association, December 19, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Bill Long and Signings, December 24, 1986 (Box 26)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Museum of Appalachia Visit, John Rice Irwin, Summer 1989 (Box 27)
    - (3 Folders) Secretary of Education, Minority Education Press Conference, December 4, 1991 (Box 27)
    - (10 Folders) Secretary of Education, Education Employee Meeting, December 6, 1991 (Box 27)
    - (3 Folders) Secretary of Education, Budget Press Conference, December 1991 (Box 27)
    - (3 Folders) Secretary of Education, Office Christmas Reception, Alexander at Piano, December 1991 (Box 27)
    - (4 Folders) Secretary of Education, Press Conference, February 5, 1992 (Box 27)
    - Coe College, Cedar Rapids, Iowa, 1994 (Box 27)
    - Visit with Mississippi Governor Kirk Fordice, 1994 (Box 27)
    - Contact Sheets (3 Folders), July 1994 (Box 27)
    - Forum/Conference at Small Table (Unknown Date and Event), 1990s (Box 27)
    - Family Photo, 1990s (Box 27)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
    - Presidential Campaign: Campaign Ad Photo, On the Road, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Walk Across New Hampshire, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Arkansas and Oklahoma, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Delaware and Philadelphia, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Maryland and Philadelphia, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Georgia, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Louisiana, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Maine, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Michigan, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Mississippi, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Missouri, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to New Hampshire, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to New Jersey, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to New York, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Ohio, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Rhode Island and New York, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Rhode Island and Massachusetts, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Tennessee, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Contact Sheets of Visit to Texas, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Dallas County, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: Memphis Headquarters (Box 28)
    - Presidential Campaign: On the Road, Meeting with Families (2000?) (Box 28)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Homecoming
    - May 19-23, 1986 Homecoming Train (Box 29)
      Homecoming Train Composite (2 Folders)
    - Homecoming Train I (5 Folders) – Bristol, Johnson City, Greeneville, Morristown, Knoxville, Sweetwater (Box 29)
    - Homecoming Train II (5 Folders) – Cleveland, Chattanooga, Cowan, Tullahoma, Murfreesboro, Nashville, Dickson (Box 29)
    - Homecoming Train III (4 Folders) – Waverly, Bruceton, McKenzie, Milan, Brownsville, Memphis (Box 29)
    - Homecoming Train IV (2 Folders) – Memphis (Box 29)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Community Days
    - Community Day: Blount County, Maryville, Erwin (4 Folders) –Contact Sheets, Negatives (Box 30)
    - Community Day: Bradley County, Charleston (2 Folders) – Lamar Alexander and Girl, Negatives (Box 30)
    - Community Day: Carroll County, Bruceton – Contact Sheets, Negatives (Box 30)
    - Community Day: Coffee County, Manchester (3 Folders) – Tug of War, Contact Sheets (1982) (Box 30)
    - Community Day: Cumberland County, Crossville – Contact Sheet, Negatives (Box 30)
    - Community Day: Dickson County, Dickson – Honey Alexander Painting, Contact Sheets (1982) (Box 30)
    - Community Day: Grainger County, Rutledge (3 Folders) – Restoration of Old Jail (Box 30)
    - Community Day: Greene County (3 Folders) – Painting a Fire Hall, Tasting Cheese (Box 30)
    - Community Day: Hamblen County, Morristown (2 Folders) – Repairing House, Contact Sheets, Negatives (Box 30)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Community Days
    - Community Day: Hamilton County, Red Bank – Contact Sheets, Negatives (Box 31)
    - Community Day: Henry County, Paris (2 Folders) – Lamar and Honey Alexander in Crowd (Box 31)
    - Community Day: Jefferson County, Jefferson City and Dandridge (3 Folders) – Painting, Plaid Shirt Auction (Box 31)
    - Community Day: Johnson City, Mountain City – Candid Photos (Box 31)
    - Community Day: Lawrence County, Lawrenceburg (2 Folders) – Talking in Town Square (Box 31)
    - Community Day: Loudon County, Loudon (3 Folders) – Talking with Senior Citizen, Contact Sheets (Box 31)
    - Community Day: Maury County, Columbia (4 Folders) – Laying a Sidewalk, Contact Sheets (Box 31)
    - Community Day: McNairy County, Selmer – Plaid Shirt Auction, Negatives (Box 31)
    - Community Day: Obion County, Union City (3 Folders) – Central Elementary School (Box 31)
    - Community Day: Putnam County – Contact Sheet (Box 31)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
    - Photographs, Chronological
    - Community Day: Roane County, Kingston – County Walk, Candid Photos (Box 32)
    - Community Day: Rutherford County, Murfreesboro – Talking with Family, Contact Sheets (1982) (Box 32)
    - Community Day: Sevier County (2 Folders) – Visit to the Apple Barn (Box 32)
    - Community Day: Shelby County, Memphis – Old Building, Contact Sheets (1982) (Box 32)
    - Community Day: Stewart County, Asbury – Painting and Repairing, Contact Sheets, Negatives (1982) (Box 32)
    - Community Day: Sumner County, Westmoreland (2 Folders) – Construction, Softball Team, Contact Sheets (Box 32)
    - Community Day: Tipton County, Munford and Henning – Contact Sheets, Alex Haley (1982) (Box 32)
    - Community Day: Warren County, McMinnville (2 Folders) – Breaking Green Beans, Walking in Town (Box 32)
    - Community Day: Williamson County, Fairview and Franklin (4 Folders) – Cub Scouts, Candid Photos, Walkathon, Concert, Contact Sheets (Box 32)
    - Community Day: Wilson County, Lebanon – Honey Alexander Painting and Talking to Child, Contact Sheets (Box 32)
    - Community Day: Miscellaneous Photos (Box 32)
    - Community Day: Washboard Band Photo (Box 32)
    - Country Jam (9 Folders) – Nashville, Playing Piano with Floyd Cramer, Dancers (1982) (Box 32)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Military
    - Fort Stewart, Georgia – Contact Sheets (Box 33)
    - Military – Contact Sheets (Box 33)
    - 118th Public Information Detachment (7 Folders) (Box 33)
    - Army National Guard of Tennessee (Box 33)
    - Military/Visit with Troops (9 Folders) (Box 33)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Cabinet/Departments
    - Agriculture (Box 34)
      Jere Griggs, Commissioner
    - Banking (Box 34)
    - Commissioner W.C. “Bill” Adams (Box 34)
      Commissioner Thomas C. Mottern
    - Conservation (Box 34)
      Commissioner Charles A. Howell, III
      Radnor Deed Transfer
    - Correction (Box 34)
      Commissioner Harold B. Bradley
    - Commissioner William H. Long (Box 34)
    - Commissioner Ernest Pellegrin (Box 34)
    - Bill Signing (Box 34)
    - New Building (3 folders) (Box 34)
    - Economic and Community Development (Box 34)
      Commissioner John L. Parish
    - Education (Box 34)
      Commissioner Robert L. McElrath
      Teacher of the Year
    - Employment Security (Box 34)
    - Commissioner Thomas Yount (Box 34)
    - Commissioner Bob Bible (Box 34)
    - Finance & Administration/Revenue (Box 34)
      Commissioner Lewis R. Donelson
    - Commissioner Donald W. Jackson (Box 34)
    - Commissioner Martha B. Olsen (Box 34)
    - Contact Sheet (Box 34)
    - Human Services/General Services (Box 34)
    - Commissioner Hubert L. McCullough, Jr. (Box 34)
      Commissioner Sammie Lynn Puett
    - Commissioner Marguerite W. Sallee (Box 34)
    - Wanda Hodge, General Services (Box 34)
    - Insurance (Box 34)
      Commissioner John Neff
      Insurance Credit News Conference
    - Labor (Box 34)
      Commissioner Francis S. Guess
    - Commissioner J. B. Richesin, Jr. (Box 34)
    - Department of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (Box 34)
      Commissioner James S. Brown
    - Commissioner Richard D. “Rick” Sivley (Box 34)
    - Military (Box 34)
      Commissioner General Carl Wallace
    - Board of Paroles (Box 34)
  - Folders by Subject: Cabinet/Departments and Governor’s Staff
    - Personnel (Box 35)
      Commissioner Darrell D. Akins
    - Rachel T. Moxley –Director of Affirmative Action (Box 1)
    - Public Health (Box 1)
      Commissioner Eugene W. Fowinkle
    - Commissioner James E. Word (Box 1)
    - Safety (Box 1)
      Commissioner Billy Jones
    - Commissioner Gene Roberts (Box 1)
    - Press Conference (Box 1)
    - Tourist Development (Box 1)
      Commissioner John A. Wade
    - Commissioner Irving C. Waugh, Jr. (Box 1)
    - Follow Me to Tennessee (Box 1)
    - Transportation (Box 1)
      Commissioner Robert E. Farris
    - Commissioner Dale Kelley (Box 1)
    - Commissioner Bill Sansom (Box 1)
    - Scenic Parkway Routes (Box 1)
    - Urban and Federal Affairs (Box 1)
      Commissioner Jimmy Hawkins
    - Veterans Affairs (Box 1)
      Commissioner William “Dusty” Roden
    - Governor’s Staff (Box 1)
    - Bracey Campbell – Assistant to the Governor (Box 1)
    - Mark Graham – Public Relations (Box 1)
    - Granville Hinton – Legislative Liaison (Box 1)
    - Tom Ingram – Deputy to the Governor (Box 1)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Staff and People
    - Governor’s Staff (Box 36)
    - William Inman – Counsel to Governor (Box 36)
    - William C. Koch, Jr. – Counsel to the Governor (Box 36)
    - John M. Parish – Press Secretary (Box 36)
    - Various Photos (4 Folders) (Box 36)
    - Commissioners Pictures (2 Folders) – Various Photos (Box 36)
    - Judicial (Box 36)
      George H. Brown, Jr.
      Robert E. Burch
      Bill Baird Griffith
      Roger Haley
      Thomas Hull
      Col. Jones
      Carl W. Miller
      Paul Phillips
      Donald Ray
      Jerry Scott
      Jerry Smith
      James E. Thompson
      Various Swearing In (3 Folders)
    - Political (Box 35)
      Senator Victor Ashe
      Representative Beaty
    - Senator Ed Blount, Representative DePriest, and Representative Ralph Duncan (Box 35)
      Bill Brock
      Representative Ralph Duncan
      Wanda Hodge – General Services
      John J. Hooker
      Rep. Lashlee
      Rep. Ledford
      Sen. Ben Longley
      Rep. Martin
    - Ned Ray McWherter and John Wilder (Box 35)
      Eddie Parker
      Representative James Quillen
      Dean Rusk
      Senator Jim Sasser
      Representative Loy Smith
      Nancy Wade
      Joe Wiley
      Ed Williams and Chancellor Dayton Phillips
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Heads of State, Political Leaders, Celebrity
    - Reagan/Bush, Election Night (Box 37)
    - President Reagan, Inaugural (Box 37)
    - President Reagan (Box 37)
    - President Reagan Visit, May 1-2 (Box 37)
    - President Reagan Visit (Box 37)
    - President Reagan in Knoxville with Lamar Alexander, Master Teacher Program, Composite (2 Folders) (Box 37)
    - President Reagan and Lamar Alexander in Office with Friends Book (2 Folders) (Box 37)
    - Vice President George Bush, Grand Ole Opry Composite (Box 37)
    - President Ford Visit and Tennis at Residence (Box 37)
    - Lamar Alexander with Bob Dole for President Rally (Box 37)
    - Henry Kissinger (Box 37)
    - Winfield Dunn: Inauguration, January 1971 and Billboard (Box 37)
    - Ray Blanton Inauguration (Box 37)
    - Russian Mayors Visit (Box 37)
    - Mayors of Chattanooga, Knoxville, Memphis and Nashville (Box 37)
    - Headshots of Leaders: U.S. Representatives and Senators, Governors, etc. (Box 37)
    - Secretary of State (Box 37)
    - Celebrity (Box 37)
      Johnny Cash
      Charlie Daniels
      Alex Haley
      Dolly Parton
      Conway Twitty
      Dr. Ruth Westheimer
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Early Years, Family, and Holidays
    - College Years (2 Folders) (Box 38)
    - Early Photos/Candid (Box 38)
    - Early Family and Baby Pictures (Box 38)
    - Early Family (Box 38)
    - Children, 1981 (Box 38)
    - Family Photo on Residence Lawn (Box 38)
    - Family Photo on Residence Lawn (Box 38)
    - Family Photo at Christmas (Box 38)
    - Family Photo and Decoration Christmas Tree (Box 38)
    - Cutting Family Christmas Tree, 1979 (Box 38)
    - Christmas 1982, Ensworth Program (Box 38)
    - Christmas at Residence (Box 38)
    - Christmas Party at Residence (Box 38)
    - Easter at the Residence (Box 38)
    - Family Photo, 1990s (Box 38)
    - Children’s Photos (Box 38)
    - Children and Honey Alexander (Box 38)
    - Honey, Lamar and Baby Will at Hospital (Box 38)
    - Honey, Lamar, and Baby Will (Box 38)
    - Honey Alexander, Headshots (Box 38)
    - Honey Alexander, Headshots (Box 38)
    - Honey Alexander, Headshots (Box 38)
    - Lamar and Honey Alexander (Box 38)
    - Honey in Ball Gown, Negatives (Box 38)
    - Honey with Various Groups and Speaking Engagements (Box 38)
    - Honey at Residence, Slides (Box 38)
    - Honey, Various (Box 38)
    - Family Negatives (Box 38)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - National Governors’ Association and Southern Governors’ Association
    - National Governors’ Association – Nashville, Tennessee, July 30, 1984 (12 Folders): Picnic, Grand Ole Opry, Conference, Events (Box 39)
    - Southern Governors’ Association – Charlotte, North Carolina, 1986 (Photo Book) (Box 39)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Gubernatorial Election and 1983 Inauguration, 1982
    - Primary Night (3 Folders) (Box 40)
    - Inaugural Pictures, January 15-16, 1983 (7 Folders) (Box 40)
    - Inauguration – General Shots, Parade Negatives/Slides (3 Folders) (Box 40)
    - Inauguration – Negatives/Slides (Box 40)
    - Inauguration – Grandstand Shots, Negatives/Slides (Box 40)
    - Inauguration – Speech Shots, Negatives/Slides (2 Folders) (Box 40)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Proclamations
    - Proclamations (13 Folders) (Box 41)
    - Photo Requests (6 Folders) – Photos in Governor’s Office (Box 41)
    - Photo Request Slips (Box 41)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Economic and Community Development; Trade and Investment
    - Economic and Community Development (Box 42)
    - Nissan (4 Folders) (Box 42)
    - Parade Magazine (2 Folders) (Box 42)
    - Tennessee World Trade Conference (Box 42)
    - Bridgestone (Box 42)
    - 1993 Bridgestone (Box 42)
    - Various (5 Folders) (Box 42)
    - Japan Trade and Investment Mission (4 Folders) (Box 42)
    - Unknown Meeting in Japan, 1979 (9 Folders) (Box 42)
    - Unidentified Meeting – Japan (Box 42)
    - Taiwanese Trading Mission (Box 42)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Bill Signing, Speeches, Concerts
    - Bill Signing – Creation of an Independent Tennessee Bureau of Investigation (Box 43)
    - Bill Signing – Open Negotiations on Sunshine Law (Box 43)
    - Bill Signing – Oak Ridge (Box 43)
    - Bill Signings – Century III (Box 43)
    - Bill Signings – Class X Crimes (Box 43)
    - Bill Signings – Pellissippi Parkway (Box 43)
    - Bill Signings – Franklin (Box 43)
    - Bill Signings – Other (Box 43)
    - Budget/State of State Address (2 Folders)] (Box 43)
    - Public Appearances/Speeches (Box 43)
    - Judiciary Speech (Box 43)
    - Sigma Delta Chi Speech (Box 43)
    - Concert: Lamar Playing Piano (11 Folders) (Box 43)
    - Concert: Cades Cove (Box 43)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Groups, Meetings, Events
    - Alliance of Universities for Democracy (Box 44)
    - Book Project – Lamar Alexander with See Rock City Barns Book, April 28, 1997 (Box 44)
    - Capitol Club Reception (Box 44)
    - Caveman Camp, 1997 (Box 44)